https://montanagolf.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy covers the website montanagolf.com (the “Site”), which is owned and operated by Flathead Village Greens, LLC (the “Company”). The Company is committed to protecting the privacy of all users of this Site. Your data will be maintained by the Company in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy is an integral part of the Site. The privacy practices set forth herein have been established to provide the best services to you and to keep all your personally identifiable information private. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy in whole, you must not use the Site.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us or call us at info@montanagolf.com .
1. Information Collected by the Site.
The Site will not collect any personally identifiable information that is not voluntarily supplied by the user. The Site will not collect any personally identifiable information when you are browsing the Site. Certain actions on the Site require you to provide personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card number, and any other information that is necessary to complete that action, but no personally identifiable information will be obtained other than the information you enter. The actions that require your personal information include, but are not limited to, on-line purchase and requests for catalogs. The Site reserves the right to store your name and contact information in a database solely for the reasons set forth below.
2. Use of Personal Information.
A. ON-LINE PURCHASES.
The personally identifiable information that you voluntarily provide when you make an on-line purchase is necessary and will be used to complete the transaction through the Site and to ship the product to you. For your additional safety, the Site will not store your credit card number submitted for a transaction after the transaction is complete. You will be required to reenter your credit card number for each transaction that requires a credit card.
B. PROVIDING REQUESTED SERVICES.
The Site will use personal information to provide the services requested by you. For example, if you request a catalog, the Site will use your address to mail you a catalog.
C. AGGREGATE INFORMATION.
The Site may use your name and contact information to compile aggregated demographic information for market studies, data trending, or similar uses that will make the services offered by the Site more effective and useful. Any aggregated information will be used solely by the Company. The aggregated information and studies will not be linked to any personally identifiable information and the Site will not sell or release any personally identifiable information to any third party.
D. VERIFICATION/OFFERS.
The Company may contact you via the email address or telephone number you entered on the Site to verify your purchases, as the Company deems to be in your best interest. The Company may also use your email address to send you special offers and/or updates solely relating to the Site. The Company will not use your telephone number or email address for any third party advertisements or notices. If the Company decides to provide email offers, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of any emails by notifying the Company.
3. User Uploaded Content.
Certain features of this Site allow users to upload or submit photos, stories, testimonials, or materials to the Site for others to view or access (“User Content”). If you upload or submit User Content of any kind, you warrant and represent: (i) that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the User Content that you post; (ii) that the User Content is accurate; (ii) that use of the User Content you supply does not violate this policy and/or the terms of use of this Site; and (iii) you will indemnify the Company for all claims resulting from User Content you supply. Additionally, you grant the Company a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such User Content in all countries and in any media and/or form. You grant the Company and sublicensees the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such User Content, if they choose.
4. Cookies.
“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer. Cookies are necessary for the Site’s functionality. Cookies allow the Site to take data you enter on one page of the Site (e.g., the desired order information) and return results of your request on a new page. Cookies also tell us information when you return to the Site to make your visit to the Site more enjoyable.
You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. However, this may affect your ability to shop or perform certain actions on this Site and elsewhere online.
5. Security.
The importance of security for all of your personally identifiable information is of utmost concern to the Company. The Site exercises great care in providing secure transmission of your personal information. Secure socket layer (SSL) encryption is used for all credit card transactions. In addition, firewalls and other security enhancements are utilized by the Site to help protect your personal information. While we strive to protect your personal information, We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
6. Legal Disclaimer.
Notwithstanding the Company’s policy against sharing any information you have provided, the Company will release any personal information when it believes disclosure is required by law and when it believe that the disclosure of your personal information is necessary to protect the Company’s rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Company or the Site.
7. Links/Affiliated Websites.
This Site may contain links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by the Company, including, but not limited to the Company’s partners, affiliates and advertisers. This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of any website that you may link to from the Site or from which you link to this Site. The Company encourages you to review the privacy policy of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.
8. Modification of Privacy Policy.
The Company reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any modifications made will be posted on the Site. Please review the Privacy Policy frequently.
The effective date of this Privacy Policy is: February 1, 2014.
Quick LinksMen’s League
Ladies Association
Ladies Team League
MSGA – Post Scores
US Golf Assoc.
Last Day to Purchase Discounted ...
@ Village Greens Golf Course
Last Day to Purchase Discounted ...
Driving Range “Projected” Openin...
Driving Range “Projected” Openin...
Book Online Book Online Now!
Shopping Cart
